Amanda alone. Amanda alone. Amanda alone. Amanda alone.
My cue. That is my cue.
All right, y'all, listen up.
Got some big news here at the Amanda Seals Troll Center.
Looks like she is no longer in a relationship
and has been relegated back to the streets.
Tough break.
Isn't that a shame?
I'm not surprised.
She always runnin' the damn mouth.
You know?
Okay, ain't nobody tryin' to yell at that.
Runnin' that mouth.
Black little loses again.
Can we call it black love?
I mean, it was both life-giving.
I told you she can't keep a man.
I keep a man.
What'd I say?
I'll bet he wanted a white woman.
Right.
Now, she knows it's for the best
and that the high power is always working in her favor.
But, you know, they had built a life together.
So, it's gonna take some time for her to heal
and her Santa herself.
Exactly.
So, I'm gonna need y'all to get focused and at your stations.
Okay, Karen's, what you got?
Well, me and the Karen's,
we can get busy saying that this happened
because she's always talking this black stuff.
I like that.
I'm sure even he's tired of hearing about it.
Cracker this, cracker that.
Cracker box.
Cracker jacks.
White Jesus, black Jesus.
White Santa, black Santa.
The blood is still red.
The suit is still red.
The states are still red.
Okay, Becky.
Okay.
She probably didn't even cook.
Am I right?
Pop the cooking rice in a rice cooker.
Okay.
All right.
Now, how about you black women
who only reads blog headlines and believes them?
Me and my hashtag squeal squad,
we're gonna drop in them DMs
and remind her that she's a failure
and she should never talk about relationships again.
What's she now?
You know she white me.
She always running them out.
She thinks she a man.
Exactly.
A real queen wouldn't have so much to say.
How can she be a queen
if she thinks she a king?
I see you, black man.
I see you, queen.
I see you, king.
I see you.
Good.
Good shit.
All right, brother hotel.
What you got?
Well, it seems like the correct thing to do
is to put together a series of videos
that defame her.
The first being one that labels her a narcissist.
The second being her continual perpetuation
of the gay agenda
going from sister to supported sis.
And the third, of course,
concluded with a false
and erroneous projection
of her as one who hates black men.
You see, the blog is how I found out
that the vaccine was turning everybody gay.
That gay agenda.
And she be down with that.
She the thing I want to talk about
we need to be called cisgender.
Sis, focus on getting you a nigga.
Brother hotel.
That seems like quite a tall order.
You're gonna be able to pull that off by yourself?
You do got a point there.
Let me call on my hotel brother.
Looks like we got our plans in place.
It's time to lock in for operation
be the bitch while she's down.
Woo!
No, if you buck.
On a heart.
Good.
You love it, damn.
Woo!
Great idea.
Great plan.
But I don't got nothing better to do.
Never liked her.
Never.
You know she got me.
She really thinks she cute.
Woo!